[{"answer": "Because I'm nothing like her.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 38, "question": "Does it?", "qSentId": 37}, {"answer": "It's 50-50.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 44, "question": "When people see you in the street, how many say -- percentage wise, just a rough guess -- how many say Phoebe and how many say Lisa?", "qSentId": 43}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 47, "question": "And do you mind?", "qSentId": 46}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 50, "question": "I'm proud and you said warm?", "qSentId": 49}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "Did you become a lighter, warmer, cuddly person as a result of playing this character?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "I mean, definitely -- well, between Phoebe and the five other actors on the show, we were all really affectionate and warm and, you know, we just had a great relationship.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 62, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 61}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 68, "question": "Squillions?", "qSentId": 67}, {"answer": "Well, I think it -- in a -- in a few ways.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 108, "question": "How did making that program change you, do you think?", "qSentId": 107}, {"answer": "Oh, I don't know.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 137, "question": "I mean, what's the real Lisa Kudrow like?", "qSentId": 136}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 149, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 148}, {"answer": "Because of the weird.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 175, "question": "Why do you think that you've been able to have such a sustainable and happy marriage?", "qSentId": 174}, {"answer": "I think it's the weird.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 177, "question": "Because you're weird?", "qSentId": 176}, {"answer": "I think he tolerates it, because he definitely -- he tolerates it.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 179, "question": "And because your husband likes weirdness or tolerates weirdness?", "qSentId": 178}, {"answer": "I come -- I mean, honestly, I think just commitment and thinking very far ahead, sometimes maybe too far ahead.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 197, "question": "How do you avoid the pitfalls, the cliches?", "qSentId": 196}, {"answer": "Oh, I met him just before -- I met him before \"Friends\".", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 201, "question": "At what -- at what stage of your \"Friends\"' mayhem did you meet your husband?", "qSentId": 200}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 205, "question": "So he lived the whole thing with you?", "qSentId": 204}, {"answer": "They don't go -- no.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 217, "question": "To Vegas?", "qSentId": 216}, {"answer": "Yes, I would.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 219, "question": "Would you allow that?", "qSentId": 218}, {"answer": "I trust him.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 223, "question": "Because you completely trust him?", "qSentId": 222}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 226, "question": "Did you find fame corrupting at all?", "qSentId": 225}, {"answer": "Yes, I think so.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 230, "question": "Did you -- did you go through periods when it affected the kind of person you are?", "qSentId": 229}, {"answer": "I do think that's part of it.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 240, "question": "Is that part of it?", "qSentId": 239}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 271, "question": "Does that bother you or is it almost liberating that you had this incredible Mount Everest moment in your career?", "qSentId": 270}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 285, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 284}, {"answer": "Everyone loved Phoebe.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 314, "question": "Oh, really?", "qSentId": 313}, {"answer": "Like a mascot.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 317, "question": "Don't you think?", "qSentId": 316}, {"answer": "Yes, I haven't talked to Jennifer in a long time.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 325, "question": "Jennifer missing out on that list?", "qSentId": 324}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 327, "question": "So how long?", "qSentId": 326}, {"answer": "It's been a long time.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 329, "question": "Years?", "qSentId": 328}, {"answer": "Well, I mean I've raised a child so, yes.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 346, "question": "Do you, where you completely lose it?", "qSentId": 345}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 351, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 350}, {"answer": "UDROW: Yes.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 354, "question": "He's -- how old is he now, 13?", "qSentId": 353}, {"answer": "I've been through all the stages.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "Uh-huh?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "So far.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "And it is a fascinating thing to watch young men becoming men, isn't it?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "He doesn't watch it.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 382, "question": "Does he watch it on television when it comes on?", "qSentId": 381}, {"answer": "-- or \"The Simpsons,\" so -- no.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "You're not cool enough?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "Well, I wasn't on a sitcom for like eight or 10 years later.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 395, "question": "Were they despairing of you?", "qSentId": 394}, {"answer": "I think I was intense.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 405, "question": "How intense were you before all this?", "qSentId": 404}, {"answer": "Brown.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 414, "question": "So you dyed your hair, what was your natural color?", "qSentId": 413}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 416, "question": "You were brown-haired?", "qSentId": 415}, {"answer": "I just started to gradually lighten up, I think.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "And then you died it blond and you immediately lightened up?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "I think people treat you a little differently too when you're blonde.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 421, "question": "With your biology hat on, what does this mean?", "qSentId": 420}, {"answer": "They might.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 423, "question": "Don't they think you're a bit more ditzy?", "qSentId": 422}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 426, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 425}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "So you learn more, ironically, because people view you as more stupid?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": "No, no, no.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 447, "question": "You're Camilla \"Boner\"?", "qSentId": 446}, {"answer": "Well, it was just -- you know, people kept asking my partner, Dan Bucatinsky, and I if we wanted to do a Web series.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 460, "question": "Why did you come up with this thing?", "qSentId": 459}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 472, "question": "Meryl Streep, I mean, goddess, right?", "qSentId": 471}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 475, "question": "In real life as big a goddess?", "qSentId": 474}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 478, "question": "She's as nice as I assume she is?", "qSentId": 477}, {"answer": "No, I crave enough ratings.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 490, "question": "Do you crave big ratings again?", "qSentId": 489}, {"answer": "No, no, I don't think I ever will.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 496, "question": "Do you think you ever will?", "qSentId": 495}, {"answer": "UDROW: OK.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "I had the power to give you any five minutes of your life?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "That's exactly -- yes.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 517, "question": "Just having Meryl Streep do it, it's almost like the pope blessing you if you're a Catholic, isn't it?", "qSentId": 516}, {"answer": "I mean, recently there was a magazine cover and a great article about me.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "What has been the moment your mother was most proud of you?", "qSentId": 529}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 534, "question": "And does your mom (INAUDIBLE) does she sort of run around the neighborhood (INAUDIBLE) making sure that they're all stocked up?", "qSentId": 533}, {"answer": "Well, yes.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 553, "question": "Any women?", "qSentId": 552}, {"answer": "No, I'm not gay, I'm manly, but I'm not gay.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 580, "question": "Oh, so you're gay?", "qSentId": 579}, {"answer": "I'll be 42 in a couple of weeks.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 625, "question": "How old are you now?", "qSentId": 624}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 638, "question": "You married a Brit?", "qSentId": 637}, {"answer": "All right.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 658, "question": "But if you feel like you want to hit me, why don't you go ahead?", "qSentId": 657}, {"answer": "You know, I can't believe I was that young.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 663, "question": "What do you really feel, warts and all?", "qSentId": 662}, {"answer": "Well, any time you're faced with fame on that level, it's -- it can be somewhat unnerving because you're never taught how to manage it and how to deal with it.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 684, "question": "I mean, how would you describe that process of going through the fame game?", "qSentId": 683}, {"answer": "You know, I think everyone has their own individual experience.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 689, "question": "Do you desire that kind of hysteria again or are you just pleased it's behind you?", "qSentId": 688}, {"answer": "The show is about Richard Fitzpatrick, the character that I play, Fitz.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 730, "question": "What is the premise of the show?", "qSentId": 729}, {"answer": "Fitz, yes, Fitz is a bit of a Charlie Sheen kind of a character.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 735, "question": "So there's a touch of the Charlie Sheen sort of character, are we getting here?", "qSentId": 734}, {"answer": "Back in the day, you know, I used to go down to Charlie's house in Malibu.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 739, "question": "Have you and Charlie ever caroused together on the town?", "qSentId": 738}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 747, "question": "And was it all I imagined it would be?", "qSentId": 746}, {"answer": "Well, a lot of us have moved on because at the end of the day we were all just people who worked together.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 753, "question": "Do you stay in touch with any of them or does everyone just move on?", "qSentId": 752}, {"answer": "Yes, with some of them.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 756, "question": "Are you friends with any of them?", "qSentId": 755}, {"answer": "I live here in Los Angeles.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 779, "question": "Where do you live now?", "qSentId": 778}, {"answer": "It's absolutely.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 781, "question": "Is there a culture to L.A., do you think, or is the culture just driven by the entertainment business?", "qSentId": 780}, {"answer": "Yes, it is.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 786, "question": "Have you found it brutal?", "qSentId": 785}, {"answer": "My toughest moments were maybe in 2003, 2004, after I had my big racing accident, I was really trying to get back on my feet after that.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 788, "question": "What has been the toughest moment for you personally?", "qSentId": 787}, {"answer": "Yes, yes.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 796, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 795}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "110805pmt", "aSentId": 813, "question": "When it happened, though, that big accident, did you fear that that might be the end for you in terms of your career?", "qSentId": 812}]